[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the flat panel monitors that became increasingly popular around 2005?", "correct_answer": "LCD", "incorrect_answers": ["DLP", "Plasma", "LSD"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following organizations is Luxembourg a member of?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["OECD", "United Nations", "European Union"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these words means dealing with charity or aided by charity?", "correct_answer": "Eleemosynary", "incorrect_answers": ["Nescient", "Parvenu", "Thaumaturgh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Charlie Chaplin film was ranked the best romantic comedy movie of all time by the American Film Institute in 2008?", "correct_answer": "City Lights", "incorrect_answers": ["The Great Dictator", "Modern Times", "The Gold Rush"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1983 cult horror movie was Tony Scotts first feature film and features a very famous lesbian scene.", "correct_answer": "The Hunger", "incorrect_answers": ["Once Bitten", "The Lost Boys", "Daughters of Darkness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Plus sizes are for heavier women.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are frogs that can fly (or make fly-like movements)", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the green-eyed Dronkey from the Shrek movies, whom Donkey calls my special boy?", "correct_answer": "Babanas", "incorrect_answers": ["Marshmallow", "Chocolate", "Peaches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor depicted King Xerxes in the 2007 American action movie 300?", "correct_answer": "Rodrigo Santoro", "incorrect_answers": ["Dominic West", "Gerard Butler", "David Wenham"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Panama is located in South America.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which domain is used by European Union institutions?", "correct_answer": ".eu", "incorrect_answers": [".ue", ".ee", ".ec"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Valley Girl, what type of food is mainly eaten during the party at Suzys house?", "correct_answer": "Sushi", "incorrect_answers": ["Desserts", "There is no mention of food", "Sandwiches"]}]